荷恩先生?
Mr. Horne?
你秘书说可以进来的.
Your secretary said to come in.
波比·布里格斯.
Bobby Briggs.
波比, 你知道
你一生中必须要有的是什么?
Bobby, you know
what you have to have in this life?
平衡.
Balance.
距离.
Distance.
对称.
Symmetry.
看.
Look.
多美丽啊, 不是吗?
lt's a beautiful thing, isn't it?
荷恩先生, 你听了我
送来的那盒录音带了吗?
Mr. Horne, did you listen
to that tape that l sent you?
有, 我听过了, 波比.
Yes, l listened to your tape, Bobby.
老实说, 里欧能控制一门技术
我对此还真吓了一跳.
Frankly, l am surprised
that Leo could master the technology.
这该死的, 波比, 你想要什么?
Damn it, Bobby, what do you want?
荷恩先生,
我对你万分钦佩.
Mr. Horne,
l have a great admiration for you.
钦佩这词是给诗人和
奶牛用的, 波比.
Admiration is for poets
and dairy cows, Bobby.
我不是很懂你的意思. 我...
l don't know what you mean. l...
波比.
Bobby.
你正站在一幢
庞然的摩天大楼前.
You're standing in front
of a mammoth skyscraper.
这只海怪撕开一个云洞
正直冲凌霄.
A leviathan that rips a hole
in the clouds.
现在, 第一个出现在你脑海
里的问题是什么?
Now, what's the first question
that comes to your mind?
你问自己的第一个问题
就是, "在最高处的是什么?"
The first question that you ask yourself
is, ''What's on the top floor?''
"坐在楼顶阁楼里的谁,
为什么?"
''Who's up there in the penthouse,
and why?''
吶, 我是一个这样的人.
Now, that's who l am.
你是这样的人吗?
Are you?
啊,  我当然是了. 是的.
Yeah, of course l am. Yes.
波比, 机会找上门了.
Bobby, opportunity knocks.
我要你去跟踪汉克·詹宁斯.
l want you to follow Hank Jennings.
我要你记录
他的生活的一切.
l want you to chronicle
his existence.
去展示那些
我所不知的事.
Show me something
that l don't already know.
2个我都想去看.
l'd like to see both.
很好. 那你想先看
哪个?
Very good. Which one
would you like to see first?
那...
Well...
这是什么?
What is this?
我想我之前把那个排除了.
l'd thought l'd taken that out.
那个房产
死狗农庄.
That property
is called Dead Dog Farm.
还有比这更糟的呢.
And it's worse than it sounds.
- 是什么?
- 反正迷雾重重.
- What is it?
- A puzzle.
从来没人在那儿住的长久.
No one ever really stays there long.
我什么时候能去看?
When can l see it?
抱歉我来晚了.
Sorry l'm late.
但那个小年轻已经对我们的
野营之旅兴奋不已了,
But the little nipper is so excited
about our camping trip,
我实在没办法
把他哄下车.
l just couldn't coax him
out of the car.
理查, 这位是朱迪·斯温
Richard, this is Judy Swain
从快乐帮手组织
那边过来的.
from the Happy Helping Hands
organization.
我是小尼克的跟进人.
l'm little Nicky's case manager.
不胜荣幸, 我肯定. 那我们?
Charmed, l'm sure. Shall we?
坐吧.
Sit down.
好的.
Okay.
正如我准备向你朋友说的,
As l was about to tell your friends,
关于要了解尼克的
第一件事
the number one thing
to know about Nicky
就是他这小小年纪,
就已经被搞的非常狼狈了,
is that throughout his brief life,
he has been very confused,
有可能是因为被一连串的
不幸事件伤害过吧.
and perhaps traumatized
by a persistent random misfortune.
看来他好像被收容所
推来让去好多次了.
Looks like he's bounced around
quite a bit.
啊, 是的, 的确是这样.
Well, yes, he has.
- 可怜的孩子.
- 就是.
- Poor child.
- Yes.
知道吧,他是个孤儿.
An orphan, you know.
真的吗? 发生什么了?
他父母死了?
Really? What happened?
Did his parents die?
出色的推理啊, 安德鲁.
Nicely deduced, Andrew.
一连串不幸事件?
Persistent random misfortune?
啊,他们被杀害了.
They were killed.
他们怎么被杀害的, 斯温小姐?
How were they killed, Miss Swain?
神秘事件.
Mysterious circumstances.
很抱歉,孤儿院从未
向我们提供过那方面的信息.
l'm afraid the orphanage has never
provided us with that information.
安迪, 我们出发吧.
北方大酒店有突发事件.
Andy, let's go.
Emergency up at the Great Northern.
看来是心脏病发.
Looks like a heart attack.
一旦受到刺激,
雌性身上的皮肤
Once stimulated,
the female will respond in such a way
会以一种这样的方式作出反应...
噢, 我的上帝啊.
that the skin around her...
Oh, my God.
看来杜恩这次真
魂归天国了.
Looks like Dougie went out
with his boots on.
拜伦勋爵的爱情诗集,
爱神性经,
Love Poems of Lord Byron,
The Kama Sutra,
小偷与女仆.
Hookers and Handmaidens.
警长, 开这个.
Sheriff, look at this.
谁又在这儿闹事啦.
What a falling out was here.
杜.
Doug.
天啊, 我真讨厌这样说, 我早就警告过你了吧.
Lord, l hate to say it, l told you so.
看这儿, 警长.
Here, sheriff.
就是它.
This is it.
杀人凶器.
The murder weapon.
她可能还用
来复枪打爆了他的头呢.
She might as well
have blown his brains out with a rifle.
他从来不能拒绝女色.
He never could say no to a woman.
你这老傻帽.
You old fool.
你这个色相女骗子,
为此,你会给地狱之火烧死的.
You sexual adventuress,
you'll burn in hell for this.
- 别激动, 先生.
- 我要把你数臭,直到我死为止.
- Take it easy, mister.
- l'm gonna shout till l wake the dead.
她谋杀了我亲兄弟.
She murdered my brother.
这个恶毒的巫婆.
She's a witch.
她是对的, 我被诅咒了.
He's right, l'm cursed.
别犯傻了.
Don't be silly.
不, 不, 是真的.
No, no, it's true.
高中时就开始了,
舞会之夜.
lt all started in high school,
prom night.
我舞伴来吻我.
My date went to kiss me.
那是他头一天
穿这他新的吊裤带.
lt was his first day
with his new braces.
噢, 它们在月夜中
闪闪发光.
Oh, and they gleamed
in the moonlight.
之后橡皮带啪嗒断掉了
抽的他下颚痉挛脱了韧,
And his rubber band snapped
and his jaw locked open,
我们就那样
在急救室结束了,
and we ended up
in the emergency room,
医生不得不打碎3处颚骨
去重新缝合它.
and the doctors had to break his jaw
in three places to get it to shut.
打那儿时起更是每况愈下了.
And it's just gotten worse ever since.
你需要解咒.
A curse needs a cure.
我懂一些这方面的事.
l know a bit about these things.
你是警长吗?
Are you the sheriff?
这么说吧, 每当有真正重大
事故降临, 我就是个男子汉.
Let's just say, when something
really big goes down, l'm the man.
小子们, 有一个关于
伟大足球教练的故事,
Boys, there's a story
about a great football coach,
名字我现在
不记得了,
whose name escapes me
at this time,
他坚决反对
有任何黑人球员在他队里.
who was dead set against
having any black players on his team.
直到某人把世界上最好的
黑人众中卫带到他面前.
Until somebody brought him the finest
black halfback anyone had ever seen.
当他,他叫什么来着?
看他跑出50码后
And when what's-his-name
saw him run 50 yards
已经无人能及时,
and no one lay a hand on him,
他大喊到, "看那个印第安人,牛!"
he shouted, ''Look at that lndian go!''
那个教练终于接受了
那个燃烧着竞技欲望的运动员.
That coach accepted
that athlete's desire to compete.
纳丁.
Nadine.
而今天, 这个故事同样适用
于这位女士--
And today, this story applies
to this woman's--
这位少女适合竞技.
This young girl's right to compete.
此外 这对她,不但符合道德
也符合宪法权利.
ln addition to it being her moral
and constitutional right.
麦克·尼森,
你能上前来一下吗?
Mike Nelson,
could you step up here for a second?
啊呀.
Yeah.
来吧, 麦克, 去吧.
Come on, Mike, go.
现在, 纳丁已经选择了
我们中最好的为对手
Now, Nadine has chosen
to prove herself to us
来向我们证明她的实力了.
by taking on our very best.
我们真正的区冠军,
麦克·尼森.
Our very own district champion,
Mike Nelson.
- 呀! 来吧. 开干吧.
- 好啊, 伙计.
- Yeah! Come on. Come on.
- All right, man.
放马去吧, 麦克.
Go, Mike.
嗨, 麦克.
Hi, Mike.
把你手放这儿.
Put your hand here.
不, 这儿.
No, here.
好了, 现在推抵我.
我会尽量不伤到你.
All right, now just push against me.
l'll try not to hurt you.
今晚想出去吗?
Wanna go out tonight?
这招叫『系』.
This is called a tie.
- 哦, 呀.
- 你这笨瓜...
- Oh, yeah.
- You stupid...
你刚说什么来着, 麦克?
What did you say, Mike?
脖子, 你快把我脖子拧断了.
Neck, you're breaking my neck.
对,
这事有点像搂抱.
You're right,
this is sort of like necking.
今晚到底怎样嘛?
What about tonight?
教练?
Coach?
嘿, 教练?
Hey, coach?
- 站起来, 麦克.
- 噢, 我的天啊.
- Get up, Mike.
- Oh, my God.
1, 2，3.
One, two and three.
现在你会和我出去了吧?
Now will you go out with me?
你怎么了?
What happened to you?
我给一个女生痛打了一顿.
l got beat up by a girl.
你对她作了什么?
What did you do to her?
唐娜, 我不是开玩笑的.
那, 你这回可真得帮帮我了.
Donna, l'm not kidding.
Now, you've gotta help me.
当着全队的面被人践踏在脚下
已经够衰了,
lt's bad enough getting stomped on
in front of the whole team,
而且她还喜欢上我了.
but she likes me.
- 谁?
- 何丽太太.
- Who?
- Mrs. Hurley.
纳丁?
Nadine?
这可不好玩.
lt's not funny.
我可不知道, 或许你正需要
一个比你大的女人.
l don't know, maybe an older woman
is just what you need.
我可不想和一个能把我熊扑在地
的女人约会.
l don't wanna go out with anyone
who can body-slam me.
那, 你想我
做什么?
Well, what do you want me
to do about it?
我不知道, 和她谈谈.
假装你仍是我女友.
l don't know, talk to her or something.
Pretend you're still my girlfriend.
不好意思, 麦克,
我可不是个好演员.
Sorry, Mike,
l'm not that good of an actress.
唐娜, 这是认真的.
你必须拉我一把.
Donna, this is serious.
l'm gonna end up in traction.
能帮你点什么吗?
May l help you?
滞留的当地武装叛军,
Hang up a local service rebellion,
想知道你是否愿意帮我去捡些
柴火来烧死那个军官俘虏.
wonder if you'd help me bundle up
loose sticks and burn that master.
马科, 马科·斯隆,
伊夫林的弟弟.
Malcolm, Malcolm Sloan,
as in brother to Evelyn.
也是玛舒先生的司机,
"把车开进来, 詹姆斯."
Mr. Marsh's driver, as in,
''Bring that car around, James.''
她到底把那辆『捷豹』
糟蹋成什么样了?
So how badly
did she damage the Jag?
还是可以修的.
lt's repairable.
在某些事上还是能做点什么的.
That's the nice thing about things.
知道吗, 她和杰弗里
共坠爱河时,
You know, when she and Jeffrey
fell in love,
他给了她一个全新的生活.
he gave her a whole new life.
那是理所当然的.
That's for sure.
我得到了一套好工作服,
和酒柜的钥匙.
Now l got a nice uniform,
and the keys to the liquor cabinet.
天啊, 我希望
我没让你觉得不愉快,
God, l hope
l don't sound ungrateful,
因为比起我以前
过的生活,
because compared
to the life l was living,
只是更进一步在荒废罢了.
wanton dissipation is a step up.
而伊夫林,
她也自己得到了很多.
And Evelyn,
she learned a lot herself.
防卫状态,
掩饰瘀伤, 恶性循环.
Defensive postures,
masking bruises, vicious cycles.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
抱歉, 我说的很隐晦吗?
l'm sorry, am l being obscure?
2个星期前,
杰弗里毫不留情的猛打了她一顿,
Once a fortnight,
Jeffrey pounds her mercilessly,
而她就想打烂他一件宝贝
来报复他.
and she tries to get even
by breaking one of his things.
就这样没完没了.
lt only perpetuates the cycle.
他是你姐姐.
你怎么不制止他?
She's your sister.
Why don't you stop him?
小乖乖,
没人能制止玛舒先生.
Sonny boy,
nobody stops Mr. Marsh.
那是这儿的金科玉律.
That's a golden rule around here.
你可以把它记下来
塞在枕头底下.
You can jot that down
and put it under your pillow.
我得回去了.
l gotta get back.
嘿, 谢谢了.
Hey, thanks.
真得.
l mean that.
哇, 它还在那儿好好的呢.
Well, it's still standing.
几乎没怎么变过.
Almost by force of habit.
嗯, 不变提供了
一个坚实的基础.
Well, habit can provide
a strong foundation.
死狗农庄, 呃?
Dead Dog Farm, huh?
那是一个老传说.
这世界上的所有人,
That's an old legend.
Of all the people in the world,
最优秀的和最差劲的
都被死狗吸引而来,
the best and the worst
are drawn to Dead Dog,
然后有几乎全都给吓跑了.
and most turn away.
只有那些最纯净的心灵
能感受到它的痛苦.
Only those with the purest of heart
can feel its pain.
还有某个角落夹缝里,
我们的终身挣扎和奋斗史.
And somewhere in between,
the rest of us struggle.
伊伦, 你最近还带过其他人来看
这房产吗?
lrene, have you shown this property
to anyone else recently?
去年就已经没人
再来看了.
l don't think anyone's asked
to see it this last year.
有3台车来过这儿.
There's three vehicles.
一辆吉普车, 一辆4驱车
还有一辆豪华轿车.
A jeep, a four-wheeler
and a luxury sedan.
门开着呢.
lt's open.
有人么?
Hello?
有人在这碰过头.
几小时前的事.
There's been a meeting here.
ln the past few hours.
你在看什么呢?
What are you seeing?
他们忘了
这儿是没有自来水的.
They forgot
there was no running water.
是婴儿泻药.
Baby laxative.
这么多白粉末.
More white powder.
可卡因.
Cocaine.
伊伦, 我们得通知警长了.
lrene, we have to notify the sheriff.
尼克, 请停止.
Nicky, stop that, please.
尼克, 停止.
Nicky, stop it.
我根本就看不懂.
l don't understand this at all.
l just had the car checked
at Gas Farm.
他还告诉我
它运行的极好呢.
He told me it was
in perfect working order.
运行的极好呢.
Perfect working order.
这都太技术化了.
This is all so technical.
求你了, 尼克,
基巴叔叔正在读说明书呢.
Please, Nicky,
Uncle Dick is trying to read.
尼古拉斯, 滚下车!
Nicholas, get out of the car!
尼古拉斯, 快给我滚下车, 马上!
Nicholas, out of the car, right now!
滚下车!
Out of the car!
你听见了吗?
Do you hear me?
你在生我气吗, 基巴叔叔?
Are you mad at me, Uncle Dick?
嗯, 我当然没有生你气.
我为什么要生你气呢?
Well, of course l'm not mad at you.
Why should l be mad at you?
我吓着你了, 是吧?
Scared you, didn't l?
基巴叔叔!
Uncle Dick!
别怕, 别怕,
我没事, 小尼克.
Don't worry, don't worry,
l'm all right, little Nicky.
要是你死了怎么办?
你不会死的, 是吧?
What if you died?
You aren't gonna die, are you?
当然不会. 别说傻话了.
Of course not. Don't be silly.
哈里?
Harry?
库珀. 这位是莱利上校.
Cooper. This is Colonel Riley.
他是空军派来
调查布里格斯失踪案
He's heading up
the Air Force's investigation
的负责人.
into Briggs' disappearance.
- 上校.
- 库珀.
- Colonel.
- Cooper.
当我们失去布里格斯的坐标时
你正和他在一起？
You were with Briggs
when we lost our coordinates on him.
是, 我在.
Yes, l was.
你在那里,
你注意到有任何野生动物出现吗?
When you were at the site,
did you notice any wildlife in the area?
- 野生动物?
- 鸟, 猫头鹰?
- Wildlife?
- Birds, owls?
有.
Yes.
有, 就在少校消失的
那一刻, 我听见一只猫头鹰叫.
Yes, just moments before the major
disappeared, l heard an owl.
还看到什么吗?
Any visual contact?
你看, 上校, 加兰·布里格斯
是我的好朋友.
Look, colonel, Garland Briggs
is a good friend of mine.
有什么你不妨对我们直说
不更好吗.
lt would be a lot better
if you'd just level with us.
我们知道监视器
和来自外层空间的信息
We know about the monitors
and the messages from deep space
以及你接收到有关于我的那个.
that you received pertaining to me.
你或许知道一些事情,
但你最好还是先搞清楚其他的.
You may know something,
but you best get your facts straight.
我们的监视器指向
外太空,
Our monitors are pointed
at deep space,
但布里格斯给你看
我们截获的那个
but the messages we intercepted
that Briggs showed you
就在这树林里
被发出去的.
were sent from right here
in these woods.
那, 它们被发送到哪儿去
就是另一个问题了.
Now, where they were sent to
is another question.
发生的这些事大概和一个
叫守日门的地方有关吧?
Might this have something to do
with a place called the White Lodge?
那是高度机密.
That's classified.
上校, 我们很愿意帮助你,
Colonel, we'd like to help you,
但你要让我们知道更多一些
这才能继续下去.
but you need to give us
a little more to go on here.
加兰·布里格斯是我所认识的
最好的飞行员.
Garland Briggs is the best pilot
l've ever known.
他天生是块料子
而我们大多数人只能梦想.
He was born with hardware
most of us only dream about.
我可以告诉你这个:
l can tell you this:
他的消失所带来的暗示
已经远远超出了国家安全
His disappearance has implications
that go so far beyond national security
冷战似乎
一触即发的状态了.
the Cold War seems like a case
of the sniffles.
引擎很好,
车轴应该还行.
The engine's fine,
the axle should be okay.
你怎么对这个这么在行?
How did you get so good at this?
哦, 我叔叔艾德教的.
Oh, my uncle Ed.
你觉得我在行,
那你应该见见他.
You think l'm good,
you should see him.
他什么都能修.
He can fix anything.
我今天和你弟弟聊过了
他讲了一些你的情况.
l was talking to your brother today
a little bit about your situation.
看, 詹姆斯,
少管闲事.
Look, James,
mind your own business.
你怕么?
Are you afraid?
你怕你的丈夫么?
Are you afraid of your husband?
你怕吗?
Are you?
这么什么好说的.
There's nothing to talk about.
我了解什么是孤独的滋味.
l know what it's like to be alone.
你怕他, 不是吗?
You are afraid of him, aren't you?
为什么你不离开?
Why don't you just leave?
没那么简单.
lt's complicated.
噢, 我的天啊, 他回来了.
Oh, my God, it's him.
我得走了.
l've gotta go.
事情没有那么坏.
lt's not as bad as l made it out to be.
哦, 看谁来了.
爸爸改变主意了?
Oh, look who's here.
Did Daddy have a change of heart?
爸爸只是做了这些年来
最明智的决定而已.
Daddy just made the smartest decision
that he's made all year.
哦, 真的? 那不能说明什么.
他做了什么?
Oh, yeah? That's not saying much.
What did he do?
工资单上有我的名字了.
He put me on the payroll.
波比, 你是3年班的成功人士了, 好家伙你.
Bobby, you junior achiever, you.
就在这儿了
And this right here?
我的首个任务.
This is my first assignment.
有什么我可以帮助你吗?
Anything l can help you with?
可能.
Maybe.
或许你帮我庆祝
Maybe you can help me celebrate
在我给老板看了这个之后.
after l show this to the boss.
那好, 你知道我怎么想的,
波比·布里格斯?
Well, you know what l think,
Bobby Briggs?
说.
Tell.
我在想我们应该想想
l think that we should think
在一起搞点什么生意.
about doing business together.
欧蕊, 你这个点子不错.
Audrey, l like the way you think.
谢谢你.
Thank you.
嘿, 荷恩先生, 过的还好?
Hey, Mr. Horne, how's it going?
其实，你这是
在这干嘛呢?
What is this
you're doing here, exactly?
盖茨堡, 第一天.
Gettysburg, day one.
南方会赢的.
The South is winning.
我跟踪了汉克,
拍下了你想要的照片.
l followed Hank,
got those pictures you wanted.
你看, 我不知道他在干嘛,
但我肯定不是什么好事.
You see, l don't know what he's up to,
but l'm sure it's no good.
我意思是, 我之前从没见过
这些家伙们,
l mean, l've never seen
these guys before,
但他们肯定不是从罗特里来的,
如果你懂我意思的话.
but they're not exactly from the Rotary,
if you know what l mean.
- 我喜欢你, 波比.
- 哦, 我也喜欢你.
- l like you, Bobby.
- Oh, l like you too.
我要付你多少钱好呢?
How much am l paying you?
我们其实还没
谈论过钱的事呢.
We haven't actually
discussed money.
那好, 你可以把这当作
你的第一次加薪.
Well, you can consider this
your first raise.
那, 你每天再来,
我们会谈谈给你一个全职的职位.
Now, you come back tomorrow,
and we will discuss a full-time position.
谢谢你, 本.
我不会让你失望的.
Thank you, Ben.
l won't let you down.
上帝之甘露, 我亲爱的.
Nectar of the gods, my dear.
就是那些泡泡.
lt's the bubbles.
美酒在口.
Wine comes in at the mouth.
眼泛爱意.
Love comes in at the eye.
我双唇轻啜酒杯,
我望着你轻叹.
I touch my gIass to my Iips,
I Iook at you and sigh.
谢谢你, 皮特.
Thank you, Pete.
非常抒情.
That's very lyrical.
是叶芝的诗.
lt's Yeats.
他是一个诗人.
He's a poet.
是, 我知道.
Yes, l know.
我知道还有其他打油诗
可以用来祝酒的.
The only other toast l know
is a limerick.
不, 真的. 真的, 皮特, 那是--
No, really. Really, Pete, that was--
- 曾经有一位女士从戈尔韦来--
- 乔西!
- There once was a Iady from GaIway--
- Josie!
- 是.
- 现在上开胃菜吧.
- Yes.
- We'll have our appetizers now.
- 是的.
- 噢, 乔西.
- Yes.
- Oh, Josie.
我只是想让你知道
l just want you to know
虽然你在这个家的地位
已经改变了,
that even though your station
in this household has changed,
我还是打算让你
获得应有的尊重和慈爱.
l intend to show you all the respect
and affection that you deserve.
谢谢你, 凯萨琳.
我会努力回报的.
Thank you, Catherine.
And l will try to do the same.
哦, 还有戴上你的那顶小小女佣帽吧.
Oh, and put on your little maid's cap.
凯萨琳, 难道你不觉得
你有点难为她了吗?
Catherine, don't you think maybe
you're being a little hard on her?
我意思是, 她仍是这个家的一分子.
l mean, she is still part of the family.
乔西要为安德鲁的死负责,
Josie had a hand in Andrew's death,
而且她极尽所能
要干掉我.
and she did everything in her power
to destroy me.
她没被吊死在树上
很走运了.
She is lucky she's not hanging
from a tree.
我不相信.
l don't believe it.
乔西不会的.
Not the Josie l know.
我倒想建议为本·荷恩
被出卖.
l would like to propose a toast
to Ben Horne's double-cross.
为乔西·帕卡的
卑鄙伎俩.
Here's to Josie Packard's
dirty deeds.
还有为坐在这儿打败他们
的那个女人，喝上一杯.
And here's to the woman
who brought them down.
敬我的.
Here's to me.
敬你的, 小贵妇狗.
Here's to you, poodle.
戴安, 我手上正拿着
一份全国发行的报纸呢.
Diane, l'm holding in my hand
a nationally distributed newspaper.
走出了我的第一步, 回应
云顿·厄尔走出的第一步,
My opening move, responding
to Windom Earle's opening move,
按我的指示
都印在个人专栏上了.
was printed in the personal columns
per my instructions.
但我昨天
就已经收到他的回应.
But l've already received
his response to this yesterday.
他早就预料到
我会怎样回应他了.
He anticipated my response
to his opening move perfectly.
他在耍我, 戴安.
He's toying with me, Diane.
我要知道他在哪儿
和他的计划是什么.
l wonder where he is
and what he's planning.
同时,
我利用这2天没抢
Meanwhile,
l've spent the past two days
没警章的日子
去好好的活动了一下身子:
without badge and gun
the best way l know how:
还有放松了一下精神.
Occupying both body and spirit.
当地的中介商,
Looked into some real estate,
很热情的带我看了
些有待修葺的房产.
what the local agent
charitably refers to as a fixer-upper.
虽然如此, 那里仍不失为
一个成家立业,
Nonetheless, it's a place
where a man might make a home,
的好地方, 尽管我对过去的事,
还是耿耿于怀,
raise a family, which is something,
in spite of my past,
但我希望自己仍能面对它.
l still hope l'm able to do.
然而, 正如这次双峰镇
发生的命案所显露的,
However, as is the case here
in Twin Peaks,
原来这世外桃源里
也是满布着秘密.
even this bucolic hideaway
is filled with secrets.
和我局里的麻烦事
有关的秘密
Secrets that may be connected
to my trouble at the Bureau
在我车里
发现了可卡因.
and the cocaine that was found
in my automobile.
哈蒂探员
会快就会有结论了.
Agent Hardy's deliberations
will soon be completed.
如果我不能够充分的
为自己辩护,
And if l'm not adequately able
to defend myself,
那很有可能会
坐牢了.
there's a very real possibility
of imprisonment.
- 你好, 库珀探员.
- 欧蕊.
- Hello, Agent Cooper.
- Audrey.
这是给你的. 我偷来的.
This is for you. l stole it.
你不觉得
把它放回原处更好些吗?
Don't you think
you'd better give it back?
不,直到你看到里面是什么.
Not until you look at what's inside.
那好吧.
Okay.
我会在这儿发现
些什么呢, 欧蕊?
What am l gonna find
in here, Audrey?
我爸爸顾人拍的.
Pictures my father paid for.
我做的很好吧, 是吗?
l did good, didn't l?
欧蕊, 你何止做的好.
Audrey, you did better than good.
你已经能救我一命了.
You may have saved my life.
好.
Good.
那现在我们算是扯平了, 对吗?
So that makes us even now, right?
- 迪尼斯.
- 嗨, 库.
- Denise.
- Hi, Coop.
进来吧.
Come in.
抱歉, 我不打搅你们吧?
Sorry, am l interrupting something?
特派探员迪尼斯·莱森,
毒品监察部的.
Special Agent Denise Bryson,
Drug Enforcement Agency.
这是我一个非常要好的朋友,
欧蕊·荷恩.
This is a very good friend of mine,
Audrey Horne.
原来他们有女探员?
They have women agents?
或多或少吧.
More or less.
欧蕊, 如果你不介意.
我们有公事要谈.
Audrey, if you'll excuse us.
Agency business.
我以为你停职了.
l thought you were suspended.
是啊.
l am.
再次感谢. 晚安.
Thanks again. Good night.
也谢谢你. 别客气.
Thank you. You're welcome.
这些照片是在
一处废旧房那儿拍到的
These are photographs
of an abandoned property
就在镇的郊野边上.
on the outskirts of town.
尚·雷诺, 汉克·詹宁斯,
Jean Renault, Hank Jennings,
诺玛·詹宁斯的继父,
还有加拿大的金警官.
Norma Jennings' stepfather,
Sergeant King, mounted police.
他们今早
的活动场面.
They were at the scene
earlier today.
我在厨房里发现了一道可卡因痕迹
还有用来稀释它的婴儿泻药.
ln the kitchen l found traces of cocaine
and the baby laxative used to step it up.
你把这个,我从农庄那儿取回来的
和在车上发现的,
l think if you compare this,
which was taken from the farm,
对比一下,
你会发现它们是一样的.
with the stuff found in my automobile,
you'll find it to be a match.
- 那是个好消息, 库.
- 是啊.
- That's good news, Coop.
- Yeah.
现在, 我们能讲些
更重要的事了吗?
Now, can we talk about something
more important?
那女孩到底几岁了?
Exactly how old is that girl?
迪尼斯, 我以为你
不再对女孩感兴趣了.
Denise, l would assume
you're no longer interested in girls.
库, 我身穿裙子了,
Coop, l may be wearing a dress,
但我还是有一只小脚脚在中间
要穿小裤裤的, 如果你懂我意思的话.
but l still pull my panties on one leg
at a time, if you know what l mean.
不太懂.
Not really.
你是打算把它吃了呢
还是打算在碟子里一直玩下去呢?
You gonna eat that pie
or just push it around on my china?
我想我不是太饿.
l guess l ain't all that hungry.
想聊聊吗?
Wanna talk about it?
哦, 你不会想听我的
烦事的.
Oh, you don't wanna hear
my problems.
我们以前无话不谈.
We used to talk about everything.
现在仍是, 艾德.
We can still talk, Ed.
还记得我们小的时候,
的那些天大计划吗?
Remember when we were kids,
all those plans we made?
周围的一切
似乎都在等着我们去开发,
lt was like we were just waiting around
for our lives to begin,
以为一切都会按着我们所
计划的那样进行.
planning all that stuff we'd do
when we did.
但生活就是这样,
总在我们毫无知觉下就开始了.
Somehow, life starts
before you know it.
冷不防, 你就发现人生已经
过了大半了, 所有的那些计划,
Suddenly, you're halfway through
living it, and all those plans,
都变得毫无意义了.
they just don't mean a damn thing.
这就是我的人生, 诺玛.
我真不太喜欢这样.
This is my life, Norma.
l just don't like it much.
我们还是能够做新计划的.
We can make new plans.
安德鲁.
Andrew.
这是干嘛, 基巴?
What is it, Dick?
我能和你说几句吗?
May l have a word with you?
可以.
Sure.
- 我觉得我们可能有麻烦了.
- 什么麻烦?
- l feel we may have a problem.
- What problem?
是我们共同的朋友, 小尼克.
lt's our mutual friend, little Nicky.
- 怎么了?
- 这我该怎么说才好呢?
- Yes?
- How shall l put this?
嗯, 他, 他...
Well, he's, he's...
安迪, 我确信那个小尼克,
它听来似乎不可思议,
Andy, l believe that little Nicky,
incredible as it may seem,
但事实他极有可能是个恶魔.
may in fact be the devil.
恶魔?
Devil?
或至少,
算一级谋杀.
Or at the very least,
homicidal in the first degree.
安迪, 我们必须的找出
他父母到底发生了什么事.
Andy, we've got to find out
what happened to his parents.
我已经拿到验尸报告了.
l've got the autopsy report.
杜恩, 杜奇是
自然死亡的. 心脏病发.
Dwayne, Dougie died
of natural causes. Heart attack.
没有证据证明是谋杀.
No evidence of foul play.
那你有用巫术检查过他吗?
Did you check him for witchcraft?
那就不是尸体解剖
能解释的了.
That's not the kind of thing
that shows up in an autopsy.
我想提出起诉.
l wanna press charges.
那, 杜恩, 你是知道的
如果不是罪案
Now, Dwayne, you know
l can't press charges
我不能提出起诉.
if there hasn't been a crime.
那好, 就起诉她性谋杀.
Well, she killed him with sex.
这样足够
起诉她了吧?
And how much clearer
does it have to be?
杜恩, 今天事儿够多了, 大家都辛苦了.
Dwayne, it's been a long, hard day.
倒不如你先回家
好好休息一下吧.
Why don't you just go home
and try and get some rest.
你想赶我回家睡觉?
You want me to go to sleep.
决不,除非那个害人精
被关起来, 罪有应得为止.
Not until that murdering hussy
is behind bars, where she belongs.
我会以民事诉讼告她的.
l'll sue her, l'll file civil suits.
只有我还剩一口气
杜奇的钱
She'll not get her hands
on any of Dougie's money
她就别想染指.
as long as l have a breath.
一分钱也别想. 啥都没.
Not one single red cent. Nothing.
我会... 我会...
l'll... l'll...
哈里, 那瓶爱尔兰酒
还在你办公室吗?
Harry, do you still have
that bottle of lrish in your office?
我想放点在热牛奶里
给妙福的遗孀喝.
l wanna put some in a little warm milk
for the widow Milford.
噢, 她犹如一把火
教黑夜燃烧.
O, she doth teach the torches
to burn bright.
她高高在上
使黑夜黯然
lt seems she hangs
against the cheek of night
就像女神伊飞奥耳垂上的璀璨珠宝.
like a rich jewel in an Ethiope's ear.
世间珍奇,
美不胜收.
Beauty too rich for use,
for earth too dear.
双峰镇警局,
我是露西.
Twin Peaks Sheriff Station,
this is Lucy speaking.
请稍等.
One moment, please.
杜鲁门警长?
Sheriff Truman?
警长?
Sheriff?
杜鲁门警长.
Sheriff Truman.
杜鲁门警长,
你的电话, 3号线.
Sheriff Truman,
you have a teIephone caII, Iine three.
请稍等.
One moment, please.
哦,等一下, 后来就好点了.
然后我说:
So wait, it gets better.
And then l said:
"那好, 那你觉得
内衣是干嘛用的, 天晓的?"
''Well, what do you think
underpants are for, anyway?''
给我们再说一个.
求你了, 再来一个. 一个就好.
Tell us another one.
Please, another. One more.
有一次, 我有个表兄.
This one time, l had this cousin.
他在牛仔比赛
做中场搞笑秀的, 知道吧.
He was a clown
in this rodeo, you know.
他们那里都是真正的
高头大马, 懂吗.
They just had all these
really big horses, you know.
你们肯定不会相信
他们都对他做了些什么.
And you will not believe
what they made him do.
- 什么?
- What?
他们让他-- 谢谢你.
They made him-- Thank you.
- 他们让他站在中间,
- 然后.
- They made him stand in the middle,
- Yeah.
然后把他的小丑装
扒个精光.
and take his clown costume
completely off.
我能帮你什么吗?
Can l help you?
奈尔斯先生, 我并不是
想给你施加压力.
Mr. Niles, l don't wanna put
the squeeze on you.
你曾经做过牢,
You've been to prison,
有些话就不需要我
说的那么露骨了吧.
l don't need to paint you
any pictures.
这是怎么一回事儿?
What's this all about?
第一条罪名, 你严重违反了
假释条例.
For starters, you're guilty
of a serious parole violation.
光这一条就足够仍你回大牢.
Enough to put you back inside.
除非你合作,
And unless you cooperate,
那我会在我的势力范围内
尽一切可能去保住你.
l intend to do everything in my power
to make sure you stay there.
我的名字是尔尼·奈尔斯,
我忏悔.
My name is Ernie Niles,
and l confess.
我有罪.
l'm guilty.
我想我犯下了重罪,
当然那并不是我的本意.
l guess l'm terribly guilty,
against my will, of course.
奈尔斯先生, 我们对你其它的事
没有兴趣--
Mr. Niles, we're not really interested
in all the--
他们用枪指着我,
殴打我,
They held me at gunpoint,
they beat me,
他们还有暴力
恐吓我.
they threatened me
with physical violence.
这些是简直就是畜牲,
不得手,他们誓不罢休.
These men are animals,
they'll stop at nothing.
奈尔斯先生, 只说某--
Mr. Niles, just--
他们要我
帮他们把毒品分销出去.
They wanted me
to sell drugs for them.
我有试过抵抗的,
但我的家人就是我的一切.
l tried to resist,
but my family means everything to me.
我一家... 他们恐吓我妻子时
嗯,其实我很懦弱胆小的, 你明白吗.
My family... When they threatened
my wife, well, l weakened, you know.
我非常, 非常内疚.
l'm terribly, terribly sorry.
我知道我做错了,但,你理解吗,
l guess l did wrong but, you know,
爱能让一个人干蠢事,
你懂吗, 违法犯罪也敢干--
love makes a guy do foolish things,
you know, illegal things--
尔尼, 尔尼, 尔尼, 你能闭嘴了吗?
Ernie, Ernie, Ernie, will you shut up?
尔尼先生, 对你所受的
折磨,
Mr. Niles, we appreciate the trials
you've been through,
我们深感同情.
we sympathize with you.
- 真的吗?
- 所以我们才会出现在这儿.
- You do?
- That's why we're here.
- 哦, 是吗?
- 是的.
- Oh, you are?
- Yes.
现在把你所知道的都一五一十告诉我们.
Now tell us everything you know.
是, 是这样的-- 嗯, 他们折磨我,
Yes, this is-- Well, they tortured me,
事情是这样的,
他们用卑鄙的, 恐怖的--
and the thing was,
they did filthy, horrible--
尔尼先生, 拜托了.
Mr. Niles, please.
只说买毒品有关的部分
就行了, 请你别囉嗦了.
Just the information pertaining
to the selling of drugs, if you please.
那好吧, 对的.
All right, yeah.
对的. 那好, 他们有4公斤
要卖出去,所以--
Yeah. Well, they got four kilos
of cocaine to sell so--
他们正急着找买家.
And they're looking for buyers.
于是,为了保护我的家人,
我就说我能找个买家.
So to protect my family,
l told them l could find one.
找到了?
Have you?
你别玩了, 我到哪儿去
认识这样的人啊?
Are you kidding? l don't know anybody
who would do anything like that.
现在认识了.
You do now.
一个大毒贩
明天就会到达西雅图.
A major drug trafficker
will arrive from Seattle tomorrow.
你要在死狗农庄
为这些人安排一次交易.
You will set up a meet with these men
at the Dead Dog Farm.
我吗?
l will?
那我怎么--?
那我怎么认识他呢?
How will l--?
How will l know him?
你正找他呢,不是吗.
You're looking at him.
他? 他...
Him? Him...
你介意我失陪一下?
我有神经性膀胱炎.
Will you excuse me?
l've got a nervous bladder.
为什么?!
为什么?! 为什么你会...?
Why?!
Why?! Why would you...?
你本来可以...
You could have...
她不会出事吧?
ls she gonna be okay?
他第一次打她,
我就发誓会报仇的.
First time he beat her,
l swore revenge.
也让他尝尝暴力有多高尚.
Something violent and noble.
但她求我别伤害他,
还要我保证,
She begged me not to hurt him,
made me promise,
说什么这都是为我们俩好.
said it was for both our sakes.
那是4年前的事了.
That was four years ago.
总有一天, 我发誓, 我会杀了他.
One day, l swear, l'll kill him.
不管什么代价.
No matter what it costs.
呀, 妈,
吓死我了.
Jeez, Mom,
give me a heart attack.
不好意思.
l'm sorry.
你一个人乌灯黑火的
坐那儿干嘛呢?
What are you doing here
sitting alone in the dark?
不干什么. 就坐着而已.
Nothing. Just sitting here.
那, 看看书或干点别的,
别这样干坐着? 怪吓人的.
Well, read a book or something,
will you? lt's creepy.
想爸爸了, 对吧?
lt's Dad, right?
他会回来的, 你知道他会的.
He'll be back, you know he will.
不过又是些所谓
高度机密的玩意儿而已.
This is just some of that
top-secret jazz.
这次我不敢肯定.
l'm not so sure this time.
2周前
在双食店.
l was at the Double R
a couple of weeks ago.
爸和我, 聊过一次
Dad and l, we had this talk
聊了一个他做的梦.
about this dream he had.
梦里有一幢白大理石做的豪宅,
亮着很多灯.
lt was a big house in white marble,
lots of lights.
他在那儿, 我也在那儿,
Dad was there, and l was there too,
过着和谐浑厚,无比愉悦的生活.
living a life of deep harmony and joy.
那里还有我未来的
一切.
And there was all this stuff
about my future.
一切好事情.
Good stuff.
感觉真好. 妈, 真的很棒.
Kind of nice. Mom, it was cool.
你爸爸
是个特别的人.
Your father
is an extraordinary human being.
我爸爸
真真切切是个奇特的怪人.
My father
is a deeply weird individual.
但他那顶军帽下
却是有着过人之处,
But he has a lot more going on
under his hat than most people,
那是肯定的.
that's for sure.
有时我睡着了
Sometimes when l'm sleeping
他会用手指轻轻梳理我的毛发.
he runs his fingers through my hair.
他以为我不知道呢, 但我是知道的.
He thinks l don't notice, but l do.
我离开多久了?
How long have l been gone?
- 2天了.
- 怪了.
- Two days.
- Strange.
怎么感觉短多了.
lt seemed much shorter.
加兰!
Garland!
波比, 我想你把
烟灭了吧.
Bobby, l want you
to put out that cigarette.
然后给我来杯鸡尾酒.
Then l'd like you to fix me a cocktail.
要烈的, 如果你不介意的话.
A strong one, if you don't mind.
当然了, 爸.
Sure, Dad.
一切都好吧?
ls everything all right?
不, 亲爱的.
No, dear.
不怎么好.
Not exactly.